module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What is the center of an atom called?', 
    a: 'Electron',
    b: 'Proton',
    c: 'Nucleus',
    d: 'Neutron',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'The martial art of Kung Fu originated in which country?', 
    a: 'Japan',
    b: 'Brazil',
    c: 'China',
    d: 'Mongolia',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Florence Nightingale aided the sick and wounded during which war?', 
    a: 'Crimean War',
    b: 'Revolutionary War',
    c: 'Civil War',
    d: 'World War I',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the name of the 1980s fictional claymation blues band featuring animatronic fruit?', 
    a: 'The Florida Oranges',
    b: 'The Cranberries',
    c: 'The Moody Blueberries',
    d: 'The California Raisins',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was NOT a character in "The Matrix"?', 
    a: 'Trinity',
    b: 'Oracle',
    c: 'Tank',
    d: 'Destiny',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which French physician was best known for his book "Les Propheties"?', 
    a: 'Voltaire',
    b: 'Descartes',
    c: 'Nostradamus',
    d: 'Jean-Paul Marat',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which creature\'s blue blood is often tested in pharmaceutical labs?', 
    a: 'Salamander',
    b: 'Vampire Bat',
    c: 'Armadillo',
    d: 'Horshoe Crab',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What type of cloud produces precipitation in the form of rain, snow or hail?', 
    a: 'Cumulus',
    b: 'Nimbus',
    c: 'Stratus',
    d: 'Cirrus',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Lemurs are native to which location?', 
    a: 'Madagascar',
    b: 'Australia',
    c: 'New Zealand',
    d: 'Africa',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What continent rests on every single line of longitude?', 
    a: 'Africa',
    b: 'Asia',
    c: 'Australia',
    d: 'Antarctica',
    answer: 'd'
  },
];